Oh hold on just a minute there buster
dad I'm supposed to pick up Emily in
like ten minutes I gotta go
Emily can wait for a little bit can she
you got a minute to talk to your old man
don't you have a seat
you know sudden you you're not a kid
anymore
oh no I go to health class stop I
already know all this stuff
well they don't teach you about
everything in health class okay mr.
smarty pants so just listen when boys
and girls get a little older we start
getting interested in one another right
you know and non-binary people a
gendered inter-gender FTX gender-fluid
people what there's more than just boys
and girls now that and they're not girls
they're women yo okay sure my point is
that sex is a it's a very important
decision how are you defining sex sex is
different things to different people
I guess when what a penis goes into
vagina
what if there's two men or two women or
more more how would you define sex with
multiple simultaneous partners or what
if somebody's undergone genital
reconstruction or or is it your sex no
but I'm just talking about normal come
on dad okay here we go let me ask you
this son are you attracted to women yes
but I'm young is Emily a woman
biologically okay you're attracted to
women
Emily's a woman so if you were to have
sex with Emily I wouldn't just have sex
with Emily we'd have to make that
decision together homecoming is not an
excuse to ignore consent I'm not saying
to ignore consent
I never said ignore consent you and
Emily right consensually decide to have
sex vaginal yes vaginal just two of us
how many people do you want guess just
the two of you cause and I'm playing the
traditional male role
go to homecoming you seem like you
really wanted to talk about this no no I
don't want to talk about anything ever
again so I can go please do oh thank you
don't forget her sighs hey Dad yeah how
do I look
you look very handsome son that's gender
coding but get out of my house have fun
[Music]
[Applause]